[
  {
    "song": "ragnbone-human-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "John Newman",
    "choice2": "Rag'n'Bone Man",
    "choice3": "Imagine Dragons",
    "choice4": "Capital Cities",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "song": "brunomars-uptownfunk-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Bruno Mars",
    "choice2": "LMFAO",
    "choice3": "Macklemore",
    "choice4": "Ed Sheeran",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "song": "daftpunk-getlucky-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Pharrell Williams",
    "choice2": "Lil Nas X",
    "choice3": "Daft Punk",
    "choice4": "Black Eyed Peas",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "song": "liluzivert-xotourllif3-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Travis Scott",
    "choice2": "Lil Uzi Vert",
    "choice3": "Juice WRLD",
    "choice4": "ASAP Rocky",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "song": "justintimberlake-crymeariver-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Post Malone",
    "choice2": "Justin Bieber",
    "choice3": "Eminem",
    "choice4": "Justin Timberlake",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "song": "calogero-enapesanteur-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Indochine",
    "choice2": "Grégoire",
    "choice3": "Renan Luce",
    "choice4": "Calogero",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "song": "fosterthepeople-pumpedupkicks-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Foster The People",
    "choice2": "Radiohead",
    "choice3": "Coldplay",
    "choice4": "Joji",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "song": "aaronsmith-dancin-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Rema",
    "choice2": "Tom Odell",
    "choice3": "Aaron Smith",
    "choice4": "Burna Boy",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "song": "thekidlaroi-stay-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Calvin Harris",
    "choice2": "The Kid LAROI",
    "choice3": "Ed Sheeran",
    "choice4": "Tom Odell",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "song": "linkinpark-numb-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Rammstein",
    "choice2": "System Of A Down",
    "choice3": "Bring Me the Horizon",
    "choice4": "Linkin Park",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "song": "rhcp-cantstop-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Red Hot Chili Peppers",
    "choice2": "Metallica",
    "choice3": "ACDC",
    "choice4": "Nirvana",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "song": "rihanna-wherehaveyoubeen-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Nicki Minaj",
    "choice2": "Rihanna",
    "choice3": "Mariah Carey",
    "choice4": "Beyoncé",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "song": "icecube-itwasagoodday-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Tupac",
    "choice2": "BIG",
    "choice3": "Ice Cube",
    "choice4": "Jay-Z",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "song": "amywinehouse-backtoblack-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Adele",
    "choice2": "Whitney Houston",
    "choice3": "Amy Winehouse",
    "choice4": "Celine Dion",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "song": "chrisbrown-noguidance-30s.mp3",
    "question": "Who is singing?",
    "choice1": "Neyo",
    "choice2": "The Weekend",
    "choice3": "Drake",
    "choice4": "Chris Brown",
    "answer": 4
  }
]
